[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this film a widowed college professor suspects his neighbors of terrorism.", "correct_answer": "Arlington Road", "incorrect_answers": ["Imposter", "Gosford Park", "The Omega Code"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A study on 2,018 women showed that the consumption of green tea and mushrooms decreases the risk of developing this disease by 90%.", "correct_answer": "Breast cancer", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Cervical cancer", "Ovarian cancer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is Jurong Falls, the tallest artificial waterfall in the world, located?", "correct_answer": "Singapore", "incorrect_answers": ["Indonesia", "Vietnam", "North Korea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Frankenstein is the name of a doctor from a famous novel by Mary Shelley.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The side of the Moon that we see is this.", "correct_answer": "The same every night", "incorrect_answers": ["Different every night", "Different every two weeks", "Different every month"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which popular substance, derived from orchids, is widely used in  the making of desserts.", "correct_answer": "Vanilla", "incorrect_answers": ["Oregano", "Nigella", "Lovage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How fast is a mile a minute?", "correct_answer": "60 miles an hour", "incorrect_answers": ["The speed of the fastest human runner", "60 kilometers and hour", "60 yards an hour"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This model is famous for her provocative series of Calvin Klein jeans ads in the 1990s and for posing nude in an advertisement for Calvin Kleins perfume brand.", "correct_answer": "Kate Moss", "incorrect_answers": ["Naomi Campbell", "Tyra Banks", "Heidi Klum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does the Bermuda Triangle actually have official boundaries?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The McCallister family flies away for Christmas vacation and leaves their son Kevin home alone. What country is the McCallister family going to for the holidays?", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy", "India", "Japan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "No stand-ins were used in Alien - the actual actors were in every scene of the movie.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Airag is a Turkish semi-soft cheese made from what milk?", "correct_answer": "Mare milk", "incorrect_answers": ["Goat milk", "Cow milk", "Yak milk"]}]